Guide to the Robert B. Fisher Photograph Collection and Papers WA MSS S-2823
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Stereographs, 1850-1975; Series II; 4.2; 5 boxes
  - Salted Paper Print Stereographs
    - Fenton, Roger, attributed
      - View of the Moskva River and the Cathedral of the Saviour (no number), unidentified series, circa 1852 (Box 10, Folder 199)
      - Yorkshire Abbey's Landscape and Waterfalls, circa 1854 (Box 10, Folder 200)
        Blindstamp: "Yorkshire Stereoscopic Establishment, Bradford, Harrogate, H. C. Booth, Proprietor." Refers to Hiram Crompton Booth (born circa 1825)
    - Ferrier, Claude-Marie
      - Chûte supérieure du Reichenbach, Suisse [Greater Falls of the Reichenbach, Switzerland] (no number), unidentified series, circa 1852-1858 (Box 10, Folder 201)
      - Valleé de Viesch, Suisse [Viesch Valley, Switzerland] (no number), unidentified series, circa 1852-1858 (Box 10, Folder 202)
    - L. E. F.
      - Fontaine Louvois, Paris (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855 (Box 10, Folder 203)
      - Le Jardin du Tuileries, Paris (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855 (Box 10, Folder 204)
      - Scene in Paris, with Saint-Sulpice in the background (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855 (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - L. F.
      - View of Saint-Sulpice, Paris (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855 (Box 10, Folder 206)
      - View of a mining operation with a city in the background, possibly Chaumont (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855 (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - Langenheim, Friedrich
      - Ice Scene, Philadelphia Harbor, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (no number), Langenheim's Instantaneous Views, 1860 (Box 10, Folder 208)
      - Inclined Plane on Minehill R. R. (no number), Langenheim's American Stereoscopic Views, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 209)
      - Girard College, Philadelphia (no number), Langenheim's American Stereoscopic Views, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 210)
      - Library buildings, West Point, New York (no number), unidentified series, circa 1854 (Box 10, Folder 211)
      - Lundy's Lane Battlefield and burying place of the Slain (no number), Niagara and Vicinity, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 212)
        The Battle of Lundy's Lane (also known as the Battle of Niagara Falls) took place on July, 25, 1814, in Niagara Falls, Ontario, during the Anglo-American War of 1812
      - Port de la Concorde, Paris (no number), unidentified series, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 213)
      - Ruins of Fort Ticonderoga, New York (no number), Langenheim's Instantaneous Views, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 214)
      - Versailles Castle, France (no number), unidentified series, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 215)
    - Langenheim, Loyd, and Co.
      Langenheim, Loyd, and Co. was a photographic partnership between Friedrich Langenheim and William Loyd (1809-1874)
      - Catskill Mountain House, Catskill Mountains, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 216)
      - Niagara, Edge of Horse-Shoe Falls (Winter), 1858 (Box 10, Folder 217)
      - Niagara, General View, from American Side, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 218-219)
        Two discrete views
      - Niagara, Table Rock and Clifton House, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 220)
      - Niagara, Terrapin Tower, from Goat Island, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 221)
      - Niagara Falls, (Winter) Table Rock, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 222)
      - Niagara Suspension Bridge, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 223)
      - The old Tavern at the Wire Bridge, Philadelphia, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 224)
      - Tip Top House, White Mountains, New Hampshire, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 225)
    - Lawrence Houseworth
      Lawrence & Houseworth was a partnership between George S. Lawrence and Thomas Houseworth (1828-1915) in San Francisco that sold photographic supplies, as well as distributing stereographs, 1852-1868
      - The Colossal Egyptian Figures (No. 10), Crystal Palace, circa 1855 (Box 10, Folder 226)
    - London Stereoscopic Company
      Established in 1854, the London Stereoscopic Company distributed stereographs created chiefly its principal photographers, William England (died 1896) and Thomas Richard Williams (1824-1871). From 1859 until its closure in 1922, it operated as the London Stereoscopic and Photographic Company.
      - Break-Neck Mountain, West Point (no number), United States of America, circa 1856 (Box 10, Folder 227)
      - Exposition Universelle des produits de l'Agriculture, de l'Industrie et des Beaux-Arts de Paris (no number), unidentified series, 1855 (Box 10, Folder 228)
      - The Falls of Montmorenci, near Quebec, Canada (No. 112), circa 1856 (Box 10, Folder 229)
      - The Grave of Mammia (No. 9), Pompeii, 1855 (Box 10, Folder 230)
      - The Lewiston Suspension bridge, Niagara River (No. 147), United States of America, circa 1856 (Box 10, Folder 231)
      - Loading the Dung Cart (no number), Scenes in Our Village, 1856 (Box 10, Folder 232)
      - Maison du Faune (no number), Pompeii, circa 1860-1862 (Box 10, Folder 233)
      - Man and Two Women, Midlaugh (no number), unidentified series, 1860-1861 (Box 10, Folder 234)
      - Military Quarters (No. 8), Pompeii, circa 1860-1862 (Box 10, Folder 235)
      - Peekskill Village, Hudson River (no number), United States of America, circa 1856 (Box 10, Folder 236)
      - Ruined Doorway, Kenilworth Castle (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860-1862 (Box 10, Folder 237)
      - Sculpture Ceres and Proserpine by Ludwig Michael Schwanthaler (No. 204), unidentified series, circa 1860-1862 (Box 10, Folder 238)
      - View at Yonkers, New York (no number), United States of America, circa 1856 (Box 10, Folder 239)
      - View in the Dargle, county Wicklow, Ireland (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860-1862 (Box 10, Folder 240)
      - The White House, Washington (No. 108), United States of America, circa 1856 (Box 10, Folder 241)
    - McClees, James Earl
      James Earl McClees (1821–1887) was a photographer active in Philadelphia and Washington, D.C., circa 1844-1867.
      - Boats on the river, dock in the background (no number), unidentified series, circa 1858-1860 (Box 10, Folder 242)
      - Old Columbia bridge over the Schuylkill River (no number), Views in and about Philadelphia, circa 1858-1860 (Box 10, Folder 243)
      - River shore and dam (no number), unidentified series, circa 1858-1860 (Box 10, Folder 244)
    - Negretti Zambra
      The firm Negretti & Zambra produced scientific and optical instruments, 1850–1999. It also operated a photographic studio based in London, England. Negretti & Zambra acted as the official "Photographers to the Crystal Palace Company," and hired Philip Henry Delamotte (1821-1889) to create the photographs with the assistance of Thomas Richard Williams (1824-1871).
      - The Assyrian Court (No. 16), Crystal Palace, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 245)
      - 2nd Gallery, Telescopic Gallery (no number), unidentified series, circa 1854 (Box 10, Folder 246)
      - View from the Sheffield to the Stationers' Court (no number), Stereoscopic Illustrations of the Crystal Palace at Sydenham, circa 1854 (Box 10, Folder 247)
      - View near the Sheffield Court (no number), Stereoscopic Illustrations of the Crystal Palace at Sydenham, circa 1854 (Box 10, Folder 248)
    - New York Stereoscopic Company
      - Dam of the Cotton Factory (No. 8), View on the Patapsco River, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 249)
      - General View of Zermatt, Switzerland (no number), unidentified series, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 250)
      - Harper's Ferry (no number), unidentified series, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 251)
      - Hunt the Slipper (No. 2), unidentified series, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 252)
      - Indian Falls (no number), Gems of American Scenery, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 253)
      - Luxor, Egypt (No. 2), Views of Egypt, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 254)
      - Niagara Falls (no number), unidentified series, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 255)
      - Old Mill, at Sing Sing, New York (no number), Gems of American Scenery, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 256)
      - Passaic Falls, Patterson (no number), unidentified series, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 257)
      - Schottische (no number), unidentified series, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 258)
      - Statue of George Washington, by Henry Kirke Brown, in New York City (no number), unidentified series, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 259)
      - Tour de St. Jacques, Paris (no number), unidentified series, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 260)
      - Two Obelisks and part of the Hall of Columns, at Karnak (No. 21), Views of Egypt, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 261)
      - View of the Sphynx and the Great Pyramid at Gizeh (No. 14), Views of Egypt, 1859-1864 (Box 10, Folder 262)
    - Notman, William
      William Notman (1826-1891) was a Scottish photographer based in Montreal, Canada.
      - Canadian Indian Store, near Niagara (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860-1865 (Box 10, Folder 263)
      - Niagara River Bank (No. 382), unidentified series, circa 1860-1865 (Box 10, Folder 264)
      - Old Mill Fall, Riviere du Coup (No. 495), unidentified series, circa 1860-1865 (Box 10, Folder 265)
      - Swiftest part of the Rapids between Goat Island and American Side (No. 372), unidentified series, circa 1860-1865 (Box 10, Folder 266)
      - Victoria Bridge (No. 45), unidentified series, 1859 December 17 (Box 10, Folder 267)
    - P. M.
      - Abbots Chapel, Furness Abbey (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 268)
    - Pike, Benjamin Jr.
      Benjamin Pike, Jr. (1809-1864) was an optician in New York City.
      - Exterior view of the Palais de l'Industrie, Exposition Universelle des produits de l'Agriculture, de l'Industrie et des Beaux-Arts de Paris (no number), unidentified series, 1855 (Box 10, Folder 269)
      - Interior view of the Palais de l'Industrie, Exposition Universelle des produits de l'Agriculture, de l'Industrie et des Beaux-Arts de Paris (no number), unidentified series, 1855 (Box 10, Folder 270-271)
        Two discrete images
    - Richebourg, Pierre-Ambroise
      Pierre-Ambroise Richebourg (1810-1875) was a French photographer.
      - Beached Boat (No. 744), unidentified series, 1852-1860 (Box 10, Folder 272)
      - Closerie des Lilas, Paris (no number), unidentified series, 1852-1860 (Box 10, Folder 273)
      - L'hotel de ville at Cologne (no number), unidentified series, 1852-1860 (Box 10, Folder 274)
      - La Colonne Vendôme (no number), unidentified series, 1852-1860 (Box 10, Folder 275)
      - St. Vincent de Paul, Paris (no number), unidentified series, 1852-1860 (Box 10, Folder 276)
      - View of a street and city on a hill (no number), unidentified series, 1852-1860 (Box 10, Folder 277)
      - View of street with woodpile (no number), unidentified series, 1852-1860 (Box 10, Folder 278)
    - Sedgefield, William Russell
      William Russell Sedgefield (1826-1902) was an English photographer.
      - Nant Bridge, North Wales (No. 262), Sedgefield's Welsh Scenery, circa 1858 (Box 10, Folder 279)
      - St. Mary's Abbey, York (no number), unidentified series, circa 1858 (Box 10, Folder 280)
      - Tintern Abbey, The West End (No. 394), Sedgefield's English Scenery, circa 1858 (Box 10, Folder 281)
        With the annotation "John Ellis"
      - The Upper Falls, Rydal Park, Westmoreland (no number), Sedgefield's English Scenery, circa 1858 (Box 10, Folder 282)
    - Soulier, Charles
      - Bridge at Prague (no number), unidentified series, circa 1858 (Box 10, Folder 283)
        Depicts a bridge in Prague originally called the Stone Bridge (Kamenný most) or the Prague Bridge (Pražský most), and the Charles Bridge since 1870.
    - Stacy, George
      - City Hall, New York (No. 67), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 284)
      - The Great Horseshoe Fall, from Goat Island (no number), American Stereoscopic Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 285)
      - High Falls, Trenton, New York (No. 25), Stacy's American Stereoscopic Views, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 286)
    - Suscipj, Lorenzo
      Lorenzo Suscipj (1802-1885) was a photographer in Italy
      - View of ruins in Rome (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 287)
    - Talbot, William Henry Fox, attributed
      William Henry Fox Talbot (1800-1877) was a British inventor and photography pioneer who invented the calotype process.
      - Talbot Family (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 10, Folder 288)
    - Unidentified Photographers, Identified Locations
      - Abattoirs de Grenelle, near Paris (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 289)
      - Bird's Eye View of Philadelphia, from the State House (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 290)
      - Chûte de Reichenbach, Suisse (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 291)
        Depicts the Falls of the Reichenbach, Switzerland
      - Cirque Napoléon, later known as Cirque d'hiver ("Winter Circus"), Paris (No. 106), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 10, Folder 292)
      - Equestrian statue of Henry IV at Pont Neuf, Paris (no number), unidentified series, 1864 (Box 10, Folder 293)
      - Panorama de Paris (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 294)
      - Passaic Falls, New Jersey (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 295)
      - Reading Abbey, Berkshire, England (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 296)
      - Royal Opera House in Covent Garden, London, Ruins after fire on March 5, 1856 (no number), unidentified series (Box 10, Folder 297)
      - Street in Nancy, France (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 298)
      - Tempio di Antonino e Faustina [Temple of Antonio and Faustina, Rome] (No. 7), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 299)
      - Vallée de Grindelwald, Suisse (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 300)
        Depicts the Grindelwald Valley, Switzerland
    - Unidentified Photographers, Unidentified Locations
      - Building with a domed steeple (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 301)
      - Group of men playing curling on a frozen body of water (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 302)
      - View of a hall with Corinthian columns and a sculpture (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 303)
      - View of a dock extending into a river (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 304)
      - Village scene (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 305)
    - Unidentified Photographers, Studio Portraits
      - Three women and a man, probably in England (no number), unidentified series, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 306)
      - Two men seated at a table (no number), unidentified series, 1854 (Box 10, Folder 307)
        Varnished salted paper print
      - Woman holding a bouquet of flowers and posed sitting next to basket with potatoes (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 308)
    - Unidentified Photographers, Still Lifes
      - Still life of flowers and jewelry box (no number), unidentified series, circa 1855-1860 (Box 10, Folder 309)
      - Still life of lamp and Brewster stereoscope (no number), unidentified series, circa 1854 (Box 10, Folder 310)
  - Tissue Stereographs
    Tissue stereographs are stereoscopic photographs on tissue paper mounted in a cardboard frame.
    - American Stereoscopic Company
      The American Stereoscopic Company was stereographic publishing company owned by Roddo Y. Young (1871-1955) and based in New York City and London, 1896-circa 1906. Young created many of the photographs distributed by the company
      - Bridge in the Royal Gardens, Stockholm, Sweden (no number), unidentified series, 1901 (Box 10, Folder 311)
      - The Nærøyfjord, Norway (no number), unidentified series, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 312)
    - B. K. Photographie
      B. K. Photographie was a publishing firm owned by Alfred Block (born 1829) in Paris.
      - Interior of the Cathédrale Saint-Paul de Liège in Liège, Belgium (no number), unidentified series, circa 1880 (Box 10, Folder 313)
    - G. A. F. Photographie
      - Le Pantheon (Grand autel) (no number), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 314)
    - Kurn, J.
      - Le Temple de l'Amour, Versailles, France (no number), unidentified series, circa 1880-1890 (Box 10, Folder 315)
      - [Empty folder due to numbering error during processing the collection] (Box 10, Folder 316)
    - Lamy, E.
      - Grande Galerie (Grand Trianon) (No. 151), Imperial Residences Lamy Collection, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 317)
    - Lurin, J.
      - Église St-Ouen, vue prise du chœur (No. 442), Rouen, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 318)
        View of the interior with organ of Church of St. Ouen, Rouen, France
    - Unidentified photographer of Les Diableries
      Les Diableries is a series of stereoscopic photographs published by several photographers in Paris during the 1860s. The images portray sculpted clay vignettes which depict scenes of daily life in Hell.
      - Le sort satannique (No. 14), Diableries, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 319)
      - Démon du Jeu (No. 26), Diableries, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 320)
    - Unidentified photographers
      - Grand Vestibule in Château de Compiègne, Paris (no number), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 321)
      - La Sainte-Chapelle a Paris, La Rosage (no number), unidentified series, circa 1903 (Box 10, Folder 322)
        View of the rose window in the La Sainte-Chapelle in Paris
      - Messe des' esprit 3 Nov 1, Chapelle, Paris (no number), unidentified series, 1903 November 1 (Box 10, Folder 323)
        Copy photograph of an engraving depicting an All Saints' Day church mass at the La Sainte-Chapelle in Paris
      - Posed scene of seven women washing laundry, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 324)
      - Salon Louis XIV in Tuileries Palace, Paris (no number), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 325)
      - Sculpture work of Stabat Mater, which depicts Virgin Mary and a drawing of female figure under the cross during the Crucifixion of Christ in the Chapelle du Calvaire in Church of Saint-Roch, Paris (no number and 40), unidentified series and Églises de Paris, circa 1870 (Box 10, Folder 326-327)
        The depiction of the female figure added to the image in the
      - Windsor Castle, Windsor, England (No. 303), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 10, Folder 328)
  - Card Stereographs
    Card stereographs are distinctive among other stereoscopic photographs because they are photographic prints mounted on cards, while other types could be daguerreotypes, negatives, unmounted prints, or other formats.
    - Baker, William H.
      William H. Baker (born 1842) was a photographer in Saratoga Springs, New York.
      - High Rock Spring, Saratoga, New York (no number), unidentified series, circa 1900 (Box 11, Folder 329)
    - Barker, George
      George Barker (1844–1894) was a Canadian-American photographer best known for his photographs of Niagara Falls.
      - Prospect Park - Niagara (No. 18), Niagara Falls, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 330)
      - Niagara - Whirlwind Bridge and Rock of Ages. On line of N.Y.C. H.R.R.R. (No. 419), Niagara Falls, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 331)
        On line of the New York Central & Hudson River Railroad
      - American Falls from Luna Island (No. 470), Niagara Falls, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 332)
      - Niagara - Hurricane Bridge - Shadow of the Rock (No. 625), Niagara Falls, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 333)
      - Horseshoe Falls from below - Moonlight (No. 842), Niagara Falls, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 334)
      - Niagara - American Falls from Goat Island on line of N.Y.C. H.R.R.R., Niagara Falls, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 335)
      - Niagara - Whirlpool Rapids on line of N.Y.C. H.R.R.R., Niagara Falls, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 336)
    - Bates, Joseph L.
      Joseph L. Bates (1807-1886) was a merchant, inventor, and photographer in Boston, Massachusetts.
      - Easter Morn (No. 233), unidentified series, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 337)
    - Bedford, Francis
      Francis Bedford (1816-1894) was an artist, lithographer, and photographer. In 1853 he co-founded the Royal Photographic Society of Great Britain. He made extensive photographic tours of England and Wales and was chosen to accompany the Prince of Wales on his tour of the Middle East in 1862.
      - Chester Cathedral - From Cow Lane Bridge (No. 810), Chester Illustrated, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 338)
    - Bell and Brother
      The studio Bell and Brother, originally involved two sons of Francis Hamilton Bell (1809-1880), Nephi Bell (1843-1862) and Thomas Henry Bell (1841-1866), circa 1860. Eventually, the father and other sons, William Hamilton Bell (1831-1897), Jackson Wood Bell (1837-1918), and Charles Milton Bell (1848-1893) joined the firm.
      - Smithsonian Institution (no number), unidentified series, circa 1870 (Box 11, Folder 339)
    - Bierstadt, Charles
      - Devil's Slide U.P.R.R. (No. 1265), unidentified series, circa 1859 (Box 11, Folder 340)
    - Bland Long
      - One too many (no number), unidentified series, circa 1860 (Box 11, Folder 341)
    - Bosler Trust
      - Whiskey Or Tea, Patrick (no number), unidentified series, 1877 (Box 11, Folder 342)
    - C. H. Wheeler Co.
      C. H. Wheeler & Co. manufactured stereoscopic equipment and photographs in Boston, Massachusetts, as well as microscopes
      - Bad Ems, Famous for Gambling on the Rhine (No. 48), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 11, Folder 343)
      - Diana's Baths, North Conway, N. H. (No. 63), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 11, Folder 344)
    - Carter, Charles William
      Charles William Carter (1832-1918) was a photographer in Salt Lake City, Utah.
      - Devil's Slide, Weber Canyon (no number), Stereoscopic Gems of Utah Scenery, circa 1870 (Box 11, Folder 345)
    - Cremer, James
      James Cremer (1821-1893) was a photographic supplier and stereograph publisher in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
      - Independence Chamber (No. 18), South Eighth Street, Philadelphia, circa 1872 (Box 11)
    - Crum, Richard D.
      Richard D. Crum (1831-1913) was a photographer in Watkins, New York. He also worked with his son, Fred Crum (born circa 1859)
      - Pluto Falls, Watkins Glen (No.17), Watkins, N.Y., circa 1885 (Box 11, Folder 346)
      - Rainbow Falls, Watkins Glen (No. 14), Watkins, Havana, Eldridge Glen Scenery, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 347)
    - Curtis, George E.
      George E. Curtis (1830-1910) was a photographer in Niagara Falls, New York
      - Below Table Rock, Winter (No. 20), Niagara Falls, New York, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 348)
      - American Falls from Goat Island (No. 234), Niagara Falls, New York, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 349)
    - Davis, S.
      - Railroad Suspension Bridge (No. 249), Niagara Scenery, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 350)
    - E. H. T. Anthony Co.
      - Easter Morn (No. 6803), unidentified series, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 351)
      - Open Bible (No. 7023), unidentified series, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 352)
    - Fratelli Alinari
      In 1852, brothers Leopoldo Alinari, Giuseppe Alinari, and Romualdo Alinari founded Fratelli Alinari in Florence, Italy.
      - Ruins with columns and mosaic floor (No. 404), unidentified series, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 353)
      - Arch of Septimius Severus (No. 5853), unidentified series, circa 1875 (Box 11, Folder 354)
    - Frith, Francis
      - Koum Ombos (no number), unidentified series, circa 1857 (Box 11, Folder 355)
    - Freeman, Josiah, attributed
      Josiah Freeman (1834-1902) was a photographer in Nantucket, Massachusetts
      - Oldest house, built 1686, Nantucket Island (no number), unidentified series, circa 1865 (Box 11, Folder 356)